http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/seller/at-a-glance.html?ie=UTF8&seller=A12RLHJO9PW4L4

Amazon.co.uk Seller Profile: Infinite_Books
Select Your Cookie PreferencesWe use cookies and similar tools to enhance your shopping experience, to provide our services, understand how customers use our services so we can make improvements, and display ads. Approved third parties also use these tools in connection with our display of ads.Sorry, there was a problem saving your cookie preferences. Try again.Accept CookiesCustomise Cookies
<![endif]-->
Skip to main content
.co.uk
All
Select the department you want to search in
All Departments
Alexa Skills
Amazon Devices
Infinite_Books storefront
4.5 out of 5 stars93% positive in the last 12 months (16033 ratings)
Infinite_Books is committed to providing each customer with the highest standard of customer service.
Have a question for Infinite_Books?Ask a question
Detailed Seller Information
Business Name:wrap limitedBusiness Type:Privately-owned businessTrade Register Number:3800600VAT Number:GB724498118Business Address:U4119, Loverock roadReadingRG301DZGB
FeedbackReturns, warranties and refundsDeliveryPoliciesHelp
Products
5 out of 5 stars
The Book was in Very Good shape!!
By Bill D. on 09 October 2020.
5 out of 5 stars
Good book
By Tasha on 09 October 2020.
4 out of 5 stars
Excellent customer service. Unfortunately the book arrived without the CD, but they immediately refunded me and did not put me to the trouble of returning the i...
Excellent customer service. Unfortunately the book arrived without the CD, but they immediately refunded me and did not put me to the trouble of returning the item.
Read more
Read less
By rachel davies on 09 October 2020.
5 out of 5 stars
Quick service, no complaints
By K. Elliott on 09 October 2020.
5 out of 5 stars
First class in all respects
By Tony G on 09 October 2020.
0 out of 5 stars
template-truncated-text
template-expanded-text
Read more
Read less
By template-rater on template-date.
Message from Amazon:
template-suppress-reason-text
template-response-truncated-text
emplate-response-expanded-text
Read more
Read less
By Infinite_Books on template-response-date.
Message from Amazon:
template-suppress-reason-text
PreviousPreviousNextNext30 days90 days12 monthsLifetimePositive
92%
92%
93%
94%
Neutral
2%
2%
2%
Returns – right of withdrawal
You can return a Marketplace order within 30 days from delivery, exercising your right of withdrawal. Please refer to the Amazon.co.uk Return Policy or contact Infinite_Books to get information about any additional policies that may apply:
Contact this seller To initiate a return, visit Amazon’s Online Return Center to request a return authorization from the seller.
For questions about a charge that has been made to your credit card, please contact Amazon. Questions about how to place an order? Search Amazon Help.
A to Z Guarantee
Place and pay for your Marketplace order through Amazon.co.uk and your purchase is protected by the A-to-z Safe Buying Guarantee. Amazon automatically transfers your payment to the merchant so you'll never need to pay a merchant directly. Our A-to-z Safe Buying Guarantee covers both the delivery of your item and its condition upon receipt. Read more
Legal warranty
If a product turns out to be faulty or not as advertised, you may be entitled to free of charge repair, replacement or refund. Read more on legal warranty.
Infinite_Books Delivery Rates
Shipping rates depend on the selected shipping speed and weight/size of the items.
To determine the applicable shipping rate for items in your Cart:
Select Proceed to Checkout
Select or add your shipping address
Select a shipping speed and select Continue
Select a payment method and select Continue
The total shipping & handling cost will be listed under Order Summary
Delivery Policies
Unless noted otherwise in the ordering pipeline, Infinite_Books dispatches all items within two days of receiving an order. You will receive notification of any delay or cancellation of your order.
Privacy and Security
Amazon knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.
We want you to be aware that Amazon will provide Infinite_Books
with information related to your order when it includes products that were purchased from them including your name, billing and delivery address, email address, and price paid.
Amazon requires that all sellers protect your information and only use that information to fulfil your orders and in accordance with data protection laws and in a way that is consistent with Amazon.co.uk's Privacy Policy.Seller's Privacy PolicyInfinite_Books values the privacy of your personal data.For more information see Amazon.co.uk's Privacy Policy.
Tax Information
Sales tax is not separately calculated and collected in connection with items ordered from Infinite_Books through the Amazon.com site unless explicitly indicated as such in the ordering process. Items ordered from Infinite_Books may be subject to tax in certain states, based on the state to which the order is delivered. If an item is subject to sales tax, in accordance with state tax laws, the tax is generally calculated on the total selling price of each individual item, including delivery and handling charges, gift-wrapping charges and other service charges, less any applicable discounts. If tax is separately calculated and collected in connection with items ordered from Infinite_Books through the Amazon.com site, the tax amounts that appear during the ordering process are estimated – the actual tax that will be charged to your credit card will be calculated at the time your order is processed and will appear in your order confirmation notification.To initiate a return, please visit Amazon’s Online Return Center to request a return authorization from the seller.
For questions about a charge that has been made to your credit card, please contact Amazon. For questions about how to place an order, Search Amazon Help.
Leave seller feedbackTell us what you think about this page
Unlimited One-Day Delivery and more
Prime members enjoy fast & free shipping, unlimited streaming of movies and TV shows with Prime Video and many more exclusive benefits.
>
Get Started
There's a problem loading this menu at the moment.
Learn more about Amazon Prime.
Back to top
Get to Know UsCareersAbout UsUK Modern Slavery StatementSustainabilityMake Money with UsSell on AmazonSell Under Private BrandsSell on Amazon BusinessSell on Amazon HandmadeSell on Amazon LaunchpadAssociates ProgrammeFulfilment by AmazonSeller Fulfilled PrimeAdvertise Your ProductsIndependently Publish with UsAmazon PayHost an Amazon Hub›See allAmazon Payment MethodsAmazon Platinum MastercardAmazon Classic MastercardAmazon Money StoreGift CardsAmazon Currency ConverterPayment Methods HelpShop with PointsTop Up Your AccountTop Up Your Account in StoreLet Us Help YouCOVID-19 and AmazonTrack Packages or View OrdersDelivery Rates & PoliciesAmazon PrimeReturns & ReplacementsRecyclingManage Your Content and DevicesAmazon Mobile AppAmazon AssistantCustomer Service
AustraliaBrazilCanadaChinaFranceGermanyIndiaItalyJapanMexicoNetherlandsSingaporeSpainTurkeyUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States
Kindle Direct Publishing Indie Digital & Print Publishing Made Easy
Amazon Second Chance Pass it on, trade it in, give it a second life
Conditions of Use & SalePrivacy NoticeCookies NoticeInterest-Based Ads Notice© 1996-2020, Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates
